Joseph R. Snopek Railroad Collection 2003.0035
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series II: Photographs, undated, 1902-1991
  - Photographic negatives, undated; 1.3 Linear feet Envelopes (Box 14)
    Subjects include: Negatives of images of various New England railroads (no contents list). Note From original box lid: 35mm Negatives and Prints: 1,031 Prints, Prints from 146 rolls of film, negatives from 148 rolls of film.
  - Photographs, postcards, undated, 1905-1976; 0.25 Linear feet Unfoldered (Box 15)
    Subjects include: Railroad photographs and postcards (46), Glass Negatives (23); Format color prints (with Negatives): Union Pacific (15), Amtrak (4), Boston & Maine (5), Canadian Pacific (21); Large format prints with negatives: New Haven Railroad (6), Boston & Maine (7), Delaware & Hudson (6), Rock Island Lines (1), Amtrak (1); Massachusetts railroad stations (73).
  - Photographs, 1958; folder (Box 20)
    Subjects include: Large 11x14" black and white photograph of the Boston & Maine Railroad Engine Terminal in Boston, Massachusetts (aerial).
  - Photographs, undated, 1948-1971; 0.25 Linear feet unfoldered (Box 16)
    Subjects include: Railroad photographs (described and numbered in box list) -- New Haven Railroad (27-110; 147-329; 371-373; 479-482); Maine Central (1-13).
  - Photographs, undated, 1902-1976; 0.25 Linear feet unfoldered (Box 17)
    Subjects include: Railroad photographs (described and numbered in box list) -- Boston & Maine Railroad and Penn Central.
  - Photographs, postcards, undated, 1914-1991; 0.25 Linear feet unfoldered (Box 18)
    Subjects include: Photograph prints -- Boston & Albany (67), Central Vermont (18), Virginian Railway (3), Baltimore & Ohio (2), Western Maryland (7), Pennsylvania Railroad (7), New York Central (46), Sullivan County (11), Vermont Valley (12), Rutland (8). Negatives -- Amtrak, Central Vermont, Conrail, Grand Trunk, Metro-North, Mass Central, New Jersey Transit, New Haven Railroad, Boston & Maine, Boston & Albany and Penn Central. Railroad Station Photographs/Postcards (88) (see list).
  - Photographs, fliers, undated; 0.25 Linear feet unfoldered (Box 19)
    Subjects include: Assorted unlisted railroad photographs, predominantly in color (in separate bundles): Erie Lackawanna, Mass Central, Conrail, New England Central, Grand Trunk, Delaware & Hudson, Providence & Worcester, Canadian National, Canadian Pacific, Santa Fe, Amtrak. Also includes a flier of the Central Vermont Railroad: "Just the Facts: The Truth About the Auto Terminal Facility in Belchertown" (undated).